Yupeng Feng

Partner at Longfor Group & Director of Digital Development at Longfor Gannet Brokerage yupeng.feng123@gmail.com | +86 13718139031

Digital strategist with 3+ years of experience in transforming the real estate industry. Youngest partner at Longfor Group, a Fortunes 500 real estate company with an annual revenue of over \$50 billion and an annual growth rate of 25%. Looking forward to contributing to the MBA community with the following areas of expertise:

Digital Development

- Digital Strategy
- User Experience Design
- Product Design Research
- Programming (Python, C, HTML)

Business & Management

- Project Management
- Business Partnership Negotiations
- Organizational Structure Development
- Salary Structure Development

Real Estate

- Land Apraisal
- General Plan Design
- REIT Investment Analysis
- Business Modeling

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Director, Digital Development

Longfor Group, Gannet Brokerage | Beijing, China

Apr 2021 - Present

- Led a team of 115 employees, including product managers, designers, and developers, with an annual digital development budget of \$10 million.
- Developed and implemented digital strategies for Gannet Brokerage, one of Longfor's six core businesses with an annual revenue of over \$120 million.
- Spearheaded the development of Gannet's digital platforms, including the customer-facing app and business-facing database, as well as customer relationship management (CRM) and enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems.

Investment Associate & Product Manager

Longfor Group, Chongqing | Chongqing China

Jul 2020 - Mar 2021

- Appraised three pieces of land in Chongqing through extensive customer research and market analysis, and valued them at a total of \$200 million.
- Led the design and development of a multifamily property investment analysis platform for Longfor's U.S. division.

Product Manager

Longfor Group, Digital Technology Department | Beijing, China

Sep 2019 - Jun 2020

- Designed and launched a Building Information Modeling (BIM) collaboration platform with a team of BIM engineers and developers.
- Saved the company \$1.5 million with the BIM platform through optimizing the design and construction workflows of residential and commercial real estate projects.
- Incorporated game engine technologies like Unreal Engine and Unity into the BIM workflow, which greatly reduced the costs related to training and BIM model design.

User Experience Design Intern

Bizy, LLC | Washington, District of Columbia

May 2016 - Aug 2016

- Researched and designed the main dashboard interface of Bizy's the mobile app.
- Designed and developed the on-boarding process and an orchestrated interactive prorotype.

EDUCATION

Carnegie Mellon University | Pittsburgh, PA B.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering

B.S. in Human Computer Interaction

Minor in Design

December 2018

 $\textbf{School of Visual Arts} \mid \text{New York, NY}$

Undergraduate Summer Program

Graphic Design & Arts

Summer 2015

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

• **Publication:** Industry research paper "A User Experience Study of Office Space under Digital Transformation" published by the User Experience Professional Association (UXPA) in China.

Jul 2019

• Won two patents for: "An image-based SKU upload and selection process for e-commerce platform" and "Multi-segment interactive onboarding process".

Jan 2020